http://www.picstop.co.uk/privacy.html

DepartmentsBrandsPhotographicMemory CardsOpticalComputingAudioSpecial OffersPicStop Gift VouchersInformationHomeContactsAbout UsPicstop ReviewsDeliveryCoronavirus (COVID-19) Information for our CustomersReturns PolicyReturns ProcedureTerms & ConditionsPrivacyLoyalty PointsSanDisk Wholesale SupplierTrade & Volume Flash Memory WholesalerNews / BlogShop by BrandAll ResultsBraunBTCelestronCrucialD-LinkEZVIZGenericHamaJetTecKingstonKOSSLexarMeadeNetgearOptical HardwarePicStopPNYSamsungSanDiskSky WatcherSonySoundzToshibaTP LinkTranscendVanguardWestern DigitalShop by PriceAll Results£0 - £10£10 - £25£25 - £50£50 - £100£100 - £250£250+Effective from 25th May 2018Here at PicStop, we are committed to providing an excellent user experience and to protecting and respecting your privacy whilst we do so. We’ve updated our Privacy Policy which will automatically come into effect for all existing users on 25 May 2018. Your continued use of our website www.picstop.co.uk from that day on will be subject to the new Privacy Policy. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. Privacy PolicyWhat personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website?When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, postal address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.When do we collect information?We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form, Use Live Chat or enter information on our site, provide us with feedback on our products or servicesHow do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, browse the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:• To improve our website in order to better serve you.• To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.• To process your order & transactions.• To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products• To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)Processing an OrderWhen a website user places an order, the information entered, such as name, email address, billing address, delivery address, telephone number, company name, and VAT number is stored within the order. The other information that is stored is as follows:• IP address, its host name and its country location• the type of device used, such as mobile or desktop• the date and time of order• payment method• amount paid• shipping method• number of loyalty points earned, if applicable• any activity on the order, such as the date and time the order was completed by staff• whether a new customer, a returning one or a guest• the products ordered     How do we protect your information?Our website is checked regularly for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order to maintain the safety of your personal information.All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.Do we use 'cookies'?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.We use cookies to:• Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.• Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.• Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.If users disable cookies in their browser: If you turn cookies off it will turn off some of the features of the website.The two cookies that are used within our ecommerce website software are as follows:1. PHPSESSID - Contains a PHP "session ID", expires when the browser is closedThe "PHPSESSID" cookie is required so that the site can recognise the same user clicking from page to page. Without it, every page would be treated as the first visit to the site, and anything added to the shopping basket would be instantly forgotten. Online shopping would, therefore, be impossible.2. Session - Contains a PHP "session ID", can also contain an email address and encrypted password, expires after one year.The "session" cookie is intended for the user's convenience, this is created with a copy of the initial session ID so that the user can be classed as "returning" and the contents of the shopping basket will still be available. If the user signs in with an email address and password, these login details are also saved so that they can remain logged in when returning (the password is encrypted). If the user signs out, the login details are removed from the cookie.Third-party disclosureWe do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third-party linksWe do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.GoogleGoogle's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=enWe have implemented the following:• Google Display Network Impression Reporting• Demographics and Interests ReportingWe, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.Opting out:Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.CAN SPAM ActThe CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them.We collect your email address in order to:• Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions• Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.• Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:• Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.• Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.• Include the physical address of our business.• Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, when one is used.• Honour opt-out/unsubscribe requests as quickly as possible.• Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future marketing emails, follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from our marketing emails.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us FOLLOW US
Join our mailing list: Customer Help Contact Delivery Returns Policy Terms Privacy Policy Covid-19 Customer ReviewsUseful info Loyalty Points Articles & Product Reviews Best Selling Brands Sitemap Affiliate Program SanDisk Bulk Buy Memory Wholesale & TradeAbout Picstop Established in 2000, we specialise in digital accessories and offer a wide range of products such as memory cards, USB flash drives, ink cartridges, telescopes, binoculars, smart-home and much more but with a particular focus optical products. Read More ..
Court Row Chambers, Court Row,	Ramsey, Isle of Man, British Isles, IM8 1JS	VAT Number: 001 8906 03Copyright © 2020 PicStop. All Rights Reserved.Website:Zigzag  Covid-19: WE ARE OPEN & SHIPPING. More Info »Your Basket (0) Items : £0.00CheckoutFree UK DeliveryMemoryDash Cam MemoryCCTV MemoryMicroSD / SDHCMicro SDXCMobile Phone Memory CardSDXC MemorySecure Digital SDHCSecure Digital SDCompact Flash CFSanDisk ExtremeSanDisk UltraCard AdaptersComputingSmart HomeUSB Flash DriveSSD DrivesExternal Hard DrivesInk-CartridgesMobile AccessoriesOpticalTelescopesBinocularsMonocularsMicroscopesAudioMP3 PlayersHeadphonesPhotographicTripodsCases & BagsBattery ChargersLens FiltersCamera CareCard & Battery CasesCard ReadersCamera StrapsPhoto AlbumsTrail CamerasSpecial OffersBrandsGift Voucher   View Basket | New Account | Sign In
